The potion that cures all diseases?
能够治愈任何疾病的道具吗？
With this potion,
要是有了这个药
perhaps it could cure my mother's Eternal Slumber.
或许能够治好妈的溺睡症
Creating Elixir of Life requires three items.
制造生命的神水需要三种素材
I don't have any of them yet,
虽然现在一个都还没拿到手
but I know where to find them.
但我很清楚会在哪里
However…
然而以我现在的实力 进到那扇门内无疑是自杀行为
I must level up even higher.
必须将等级升得更高才行
I must…
必须…
become stronger.
变得更强
Eh, you decided to accept it?
什么？大哥同意了吗？
For your proposal for 19 C-rank raid missions, I'm in.
你提出的参加19次C级突击任务计划
That's great.
太棒了
But I have one condition.
但我有一个条件
Just say it.
好 尽管说吧
Just you and me.
就我跟你两个人去
Just the two of us to conquer C-rank dungeons?
意思是靠我跟大哥两人 去攻掠C级地下城？
That's right.
正是如此
But… to enter the C-rank gate,
但是要进入C级传送门
we need at least eight people, don't we?
至少需要八个人不是吗？
Just find people to make up the numbers,
找人来凑就行了
like what Hwang Dongsuk did.
可以用黄东石用过的那个方法
B-But…
可是这样会不会太危险？
It depends on how you see it.
这要看你怎么想
As long as the two of us are safe,
要是顺利的话 我们就能在无人受伤的状况下
A team unscathed in 19 consecutive missions.
连续19次无人伤亡的攻击队
Isn't that a perfect way to make your father acknowledge you?
这不是让你老爸 认同你实力的绝佳材料吗？
I see.
原来如此呀
Let's do it, Jinwoo.
就这么做吧 大哥！
I'll take care of team members and the gate.
队员与传送门就由我来安排
Come out.
你找我有什么事？
Truly surprising.
真是令人吃惊
No wonder you're an S-rank hunter.
不愧是S级猎人
I couldn't find the right moment to speak to you.
我一直在找适当的时机向您搭话
Sorry for disturbing you during your training.
抱歉在训练时打扰您
Here is my business card.
这是我的名片
It's been over a decade since the gates appeared.
传送门出现至今已十余年
The world has changed drastically.
世界出现了翻天覆地的变化
Now infrastructure, economy, media, and even politics
如今基础建设、经济 媒体 甚至是政治
are all inextricably linked to the dungeon.
各方面都跟地下城脱离不了关系
Especially the infrastructure that is vital to the common people.
特别是与百姓的生活 息息相关的基础建设
And the only ones who can bring such valuable resources back
而唯一能将如此贵重的资源 带回这个世界的
are the hunters.
就是猎人
And the one managing these hunters
而管理那些猎人的
is the government agency known as Hunter's Association.
就是名为“猎人协会”的公家机关
The Hunter's Association will classify awakened hunters,
猎人协会会对觉醒的 猎人进行等级判定
register and manage them accordingly.
完成登录 并加以管理
They assign manpower to deal with unwanted gates
安排人手处理遗漏的传送门
and also bear the heavy responsibility in Dungeon Breaks.
也肩负着传送门 解除封印时的应对处理
But in the end, the association is just a government agency.
但协会终究只是个公家机关
Most of the resources needed to sustain our society are brought back
实际上 为了维持社会运作
by guilds, the corporations that center around hunters.
是名为“公会” 这个以猎人行业为主轴的企业
The guilds obtain massive profits from the resources
公会能从地下城取得资源
acquired from the dungeons.
从中获取庞大利益
Among them, Hunters Guild, White Tiger Guild,
其中又以汉特斯公会、白虎公会
Feind Guild, Fame Guild, and Knights Guild
死神公会、明星公会、骑士团公会
are the five major guilds in the country.
这国内五大公会为大宗
These guilds have almost monopolized all the resources.
可以说这些公会几乎占据了所有利益
I cannot just sit here and watch.
面对这个状况 我不能只是心有不甘地旁观
Not to mention letting these resources vital to the people
更别说让这些 可称为人民生命线的资源
fall into the hands of those brutes.
落在一些只会行使蛮力之人的手上
It should be us, who have supported the nation's development,
我们扶持国家发展至今
to take on the responsibility to manage them.
应该要由我们负责保管资源
For this purpose,
为了这个目的
we must establish a guild.
成立公会一事势在必行
Yes.
是
That being said,
话虽如此
headhunting S-rank hunters to make them run a guild with my brother
挖角S级猎人
But,
但是现在的我…
It stopped counting the quests that exceeded the goal?
超过任务要求的训练量 已经不列入计算了吗？
Does it mean I can't get the reward for the previous secret quest,
果然之前的隐藏任务奖励 受诅咒的随机宝箱
the Cursed Random Loot Box?
当时没选就没机会拿了啊
I thought I could get another item like the Demon Castle's Key.
我还以为能再得到 跟恶魔城的钥匙有同等价值的道具呢
No.
不对
Even if it's a regular random box,
就算是一般的随机宝箱
it's possible to get something like an instance dungeon's key.
也还是有可能像上次那样 开出副本地下城钥匙之类的东西
Or maybe not.
我想也是
At this level, three ability points are no longer enough.
能力值提升到这个阶段
I really want to level up quickly,
虽然很想快点把等级升起来
but now I can only wait for Jinho's C-rank dungeon missions.
但如今只能等待 轸皓的C级地下城任务通知
If I kill those centipedes there…
只要干掉那里的蜈蚣…
No.
不行
Now I might escape more easily than before.
现在或许能逃得比那时轻松
But to defeat it…
但要打倒它的话…
Besides, I might not be able to gain any points.
况且也不一定能得到经验值
D-rank gate mission?
D级传送门的任务召集令？
It's a request from the Hunter's Association for making up a team,
是猎人协会的攻击队组队邀请
which means I can't fight alone.
也就是说无法独自战斗
Should I refuse?
要拒绝吗？
Well, it's better than nothing.
算了 聊胜于无
I have no time to waste.
真是令人心急
I still can't defeat you, Master.
我果然还是赢不过师父
It won't be so easy for you to defeat me.
要赢我没那么容易
However, it's still a pity.
不过我还是觉得很遗憾
I wanted to face off against you in your top condition.
我真的很想跟万全状态下的师父交手
You're bringing this up again.
又在提那件事
It's been several months.
明明都过好几个月了
An urgent call-up?
紧急召集吗？
Low-rank hunters are just fated to run errands.
下级猎人就是常有一堆杂事找上门
Master, have you never thought about retiring?
师父 您真的没想过要引退吗？
Indeed.
一个失去一条手臂的老头
No, that's not what I meant…
不是的 我不是那个意思！
I lost an arm, yet I survived.
虽然失去一臂 却保住了一命
I don't have much time left.
我这条老命已没几年可活了
At least before I die, I hope to do more for this world.
希望至少在死前 能为这个世界再多做一些贡献
I got a new raid mission.
下一个突击任务来了
Dear.
老公
Isn't it about time you give up being a hunter?
你也差不多 该放下猎人这个工作了吧？
You bring it up again?
又说这个吗？
Because it's too dangerous.
因为实在太危险了
So many people died in the last mission.
之前的突击任务 也出现了那么多牺牲者
You almost didn't make it out, right?
你不也是在千钧一发之际 好不容易逃出来的吗？
Hmm… Yeah.
嗯？是啊
Daddy, hug.
爸爸 抱抱
But, next year, Eunji will be going to kindergarten,
但是明年恩知就要上幼儿园
and Eunha is also going to junior high.
恩霞也要上初中了
We need money, don't we?
我们需要钱不是吗？
That's true, but still…
是这样没错啦
It's okay.
没问题的
The association wouldn't send us low-rank hunters to overly dangerous dungeons.
协会也不会叫我们这种下级猎人 去处理太过危险的地下城
Last time was just an exception.
上次只是例外
Yes.
也对
Sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
抱歉 我不该多嘴的
Don't mind it.
别在意
Be careful, okay?
你要小心喔
Okay.
好 我爱你
Daddy.
爸爸
Daddy, are you very powerful?
爸爸很厉害吗？
Of course.
那当然啊
I can defeat scary monsters.
爸爸可是连恐怖的怪物都能打倒呢
That's amazing.
好厉害
Daddy, you really are the best.
爸爸果然最厉害了
You tricked me.
你居然摆了我一道
What are you referring to?
你是指什么事呢？
You pushed the bothersome media interview onto me.
竟然把媒体访谈这种麻烦事推给我
I saw it on TV.
我在电视上看到了
You did super well.
你表现得很好
Your speech really hit home.
那些发言简直说到我心坎里
Stop saying that.
少跟我说这些违心之论
That was originally your job, right?
更何况那工作本来是发给你的吧？
to show the public the work attitude and honest character of strong hunters.
“让民众看见强大猎人 对于工作的真挚与诚实的为人”
I don't think I'm quite suited for this task.
我认为自己并不太适合这项任务
So you know you're not honest.
你也知道自己看起来不可信啊
Forget it.
算了
All right, what do you want from me?
好了 找我做什么？
You didn't summon me just to hear me complain, right?
你不可能是为了听我抱怨 才特地叫我来吧？
I must inform you of a recent event.
因为发生了我认为 应该要让你知道一下的事
Yoojin Construction seems to want to establish a guild.
柳轸建设似乎有动作了 看来是想成立公会
I know that. They are looking for people under the table.
这我知道 他们似乎在台面下做了不少小动作
I've also heard they are poaching my people.
也听说他们在挖角我这边的人
Since you have known it, it seems I am meddling unnecessarily.
真是意外 既然你已经知情 那看来是我多管闲事了
You knew all along that I would know.
你早就明白我已经知道了吧？
Stop beating around the bush.
少在那边拐弯抹角
I'll ask you again.
我再问你一次
What do you want from me?
找我做什么？
You haven't been calling recently.
你最近都没打电话回来
Is everything going well?
过得还好吗？
It's okay.
还行
You have always been timid.
你从以前就很胆小
Doesn't working as a hunter make you uncomfortable?
从事猎人这种工作 不就是自找罪受吗？
I heard you're a B-rank hunter.
听说是B级对吧？
If it were someone else, they would probably be strong.
如果是别人 那可能会有一定的实力
But you'd probably be a burden to others.
不过你的话 只会拖别人的后腿吧
You'd better come back and help out at home.
还是回来帮家里的忙吧
Your dad is also worried--
你爸也很担心你…
Don't make decisions for me, okay?
不要只讲你自己想讲的！
I'll make my own decisions. I don't need you to interfere.
我自己的事 自己会做决定 不用你管！
Wait, why are you--
等一下 你干吗这样？
A burden to others?
会拖别人后腿？
But…
但是…
I'll just give it another go.
再试着努力看看吧
Excuse me.
打扰了
What is it, Hunter Cha Hae-In?
有什么事吗 车海印猎人？
Someone from Yoojin Construction tried to poach me during my training.
不久前我在训练时 柳轸建设的人来挖角我
I came to report to you.
所以来向你报告一下
I see.
这样啊
It seems they want to establish a new guild
他们似乎是要成立新的公会
and want me to be the guild master.
希望我过去担任公会长一职
You've come to report to me.
你来找我报告
Can I take it as you've declined their offer?
也就是说 我能当作你拒绝了他吗？
Yes. I declined right on the spot.
是的 我当场就回绝了
I'm relieved.
那我放心了 谢谢你
It's nothing.
不会
By the way,
话说回来
I saw Mr. Baek on my way here.
在过来的路上 我见到了白社长
What did he come to talk to you about?
他是来找你谈什么呢？
What are your thoughts on Jeju Island?
关于济州岛的事 你有什么想法？
Jeju Island?
济州岛？
Why do you ask that?
你这样问是什么意思？
After the third raid mission, the island was ordered off-limits.
在第三次突击任务后 那座岛就被下令禁止进入
Now, there are only periodic patrols along the coast.
现在只有从沿岸进行定期侦查
And the public only sees the annual memorial service.
以及让大众知道 每年会在那里举办一次慰灵仪式
People have forgotten the island along with the fear.
人们正将那座岛随着恐惧一起遗忘掉
But that's unavoidable, isn't it?
但那也是没办法的不是吗？
However,
但是…
whether the gates have become part of daily life,
不管传送门的出现 成为多么普通的日常景象
or I'm hailed as the Ultimate Weapon of Mankind,
还被世人吹捧我为人类最终兵器
I will not forget that island, nor what happened there.
我不曾忘记那座岛 以及在岛上发生过的事
In the near future,
我在不远的将来
I will definitely conquer that island.
一定会再度攻掠那座岛
For that reason,
为此你们现在不能分崩离析 不然我会很头疼
We must unite, increase our numbers,
我们必须加强实力 增加同伴
and sway public opinion.
并且带动舆论风向
That's what those interviews and nurturing of newcomers are for?
那些采访与培育新人 都是为了此目的吗？
Aren't you the same?
你不也是一样吗？
You have also left something behind on that island.
一样有东西遗落在那座岛上
Eunseok.
恩硕
Byung-gu.
炳久
Please.
拜托你
Help me…
帮我…
kill them.
杀了那些家伙
I'm going out.
我出门了
Still working on the holiday?
今天假日 你还要去工作喔？
You've been doing this often lately.
你最近经常这样耶
Yes.
是啊
You used to get hurt every time you went through the gate.
明明直到不久前每次进传送门 都会弄得满身是伤 休息很久
Is this the result of exercise?
这是锻炼的成果吗？
Perhaps.
可能喔
Anyway, I can earn money steadily now. Isn't that a good thing?
总之我现在能稳定地赚钱了
It is…
是没错啦
Eh, Brother? Don't you need luggage?
等等 哥 你不用带行李吗？
No need. I'm heading out.
不用啦 那我出门了
Eh, wait.
什么？等一下啦
It's not like going to the convenience store.
又不是去便利商店买东西
My awakening is not a physical type of awakening.
并非觉醒成物理型猎人的我 所使出的剑术
My swordsmanship can't harm the magic beasts.
无法对魔兽造成伤害
The swordsmanship that I've practiced for decades
练了几十年的剑术 在地下城里居然派不上一点用场
The fact that I, a swordsman, awakened as a mage is also a twist of fate.
我一介剑士觉醒为法师型猎人 也是命运使然
Could there be some reason behind it?
其中或许也有什么原由吧
You are…
你是…
Mr. Song.
宋大叔
I was wondering if I was mistaken.
我还在想是不是认错人了
Are you Sung?
你不是阿成吗？
Long time no see.
好久不见了
I never thought that I would see you here again.
想不到居然能在这里见到你
where is that immature young man?
那个稚气未脱的少年跑去哪里了？
In just a few months, you've changed so much.
才短短几个月 居然就变了这么多
And…
而且啊
How come your leg is fine?
你那条被砍断的腿怎么没事？
I see.
这样啊
There might be a high-level healer among the hunters who came to rescue.
可能是后来来救援的猎人中 有上级的治疗师在吧
Regardless,
不管怎么说
it's great to see a young talent making a recovery.
看到前途无量的年轻人能复原 实在是太好了
Thank you.
谢谢你
But you…
但是宋大叔你…
As for me,
我似乎在受伤后拖了太久
But it's all right.
但是无妨
What's more important is,
更重要的是
I heard from the association staff that you are all right,
虽然从协会人员那里听说你没事
but I'm glad to be able to see you like this again.
但还能再这样和你相见 我很高兴
Mr. Song, why did you come here?
宋大叔 你怎么会来这里？
I was summoned by the association. I heard that it's a D-rank mission.
是被协会找来的
You are in it too?
你也要参加吗？
I can't believe this.
居然这么巧
The members from that mission.
没想到那天的任务成员都来了
Jinwoo.
振宇？
Joohee.
珠熙
And
还有…
Mr. Kim and Mr. Kang.
金大叔和姜先生
So be it.
这也没办法
After all, we abandoned Sung and fled that place.
毕竟那一天我们丢下阿成 逃离了那个地方
Kim even drew his sword against me.
老金甚至对我举剑相向
I suppose he is too ashamed to face us.
他一定更没脸见我们
But…
但是…
The five survivors of that tragedy are once again together.
在那场惨剧里幸存的五人 再度这样齐聚一堂
So…
这表示…
Jinwoo.
振宇
It's you, right?
是你对吧？
You've changed a lot.
你看起来变了好多
Yes. It's been a long time.
是啊 好久不见
You've grown much taller.
也长高了不少
And your leg.
你的脚也是…
When I came to visit, you were already…
果然我去探病的时候 你就已经…
Visit?
什么？探病？
There's a beautiful lady here too.
这里也有年轻小姐啊
What's the matter?
怎么啦？
Are you with that young man?
你跟那位小哥搞上了吗？
Why don't you come to us--
也过来跟我们玩玩嘛…
Shut up.
给我闭嘴
You are not here for a hike.
你们可不是来远足的
Now, I will explain to all the general hunters.
现在要跟所有的一般猎人进行说明
Please come this way.
请过来这边
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Substitute prisoners?
“替代服刑者”？
We have to go on a mission with criminals?
你是要我们跟罪犯一起共斗吗？
Although they are hunters with convictions,
他们虽然是有罪在身的猎人
they wish to lessen their sentences, so they will not harm you.
但都是些想减轻刑罚的犯人 所以不会做出危险行为
There is a shortage of manpower in this area.
现在这个地区的猎人减少 人手不足
Please bear with us.
还请各位谅解
How can this be?
怎么会这样？
Kang Taeshik from Hunter's Association's Surveillance Team will accompany you.
这次猎人协会监察科的姜泰植 也会与各位同行
He is a B-rank hunter.
他是B级猎人
Even in the event of danger, he can easily deal with three C-rank prisoners.
就算发生危险情况
So please rest assured.
所以请各位放心
Something feels wrong.
我感觉有些不安
Joohee, you shouldn't go.
珠熙 你这次就别参加了
What about you?
那你呢？
I'm going.
我要进去
Then I'm going too.
那我也要去
I understand.
我明白了
We are not slaves.
我们又不是奴隶
Do you have to treat us this way?
有必要这样对待我们吗？
Shut up.
闭嘴
You are prisoners.
你们是囚犯
If you dare to make a reckless move, you know what will happen to you.
要是敢轻举妄动 知道自己会有什么下场吧？
I'm Kang Taeshik from the Hunter's Association's Surveillance Team.
我是猎人协会监察科的姜泰植
I will take responsibility for monitoring them.
我会负起责任监视他们
Please be assured.
还请各位放心
Who will be the leader of this raid mission?
请问谁要担任本次突击任务的领队？
Sung, can I be the captain?
阿成 可以让我来当吗？
Yes, of course.
是 当然好
Thank you for giving me another chance.
谢谢你愿意再次给我机会
Mr. Song.
宋大叔？
That day, due to my mistake, seven people lost their lives.
那天因为我的错让七个人白白送命
I am to blame for not being able to protect them.
没能保护众人 我责无旁贷
But, thanks to you, six people survived.
但是多亏有你 才让另外六个人活了下来
Please allow me to thank you on behalf of the five of them.
请让我代替除了你之外的五人 向你道谢
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
我打从心底感谢你
Mr. Song. Please raise your head.
宋大叔 请抬起头来
Kim, are you okay with me being the captain?
老金 由我来当队长 你也没意见吧？
Whatever.
随便你
That's it then.
事情就是这样
I'll lead the team in the dungeon.
在地下城里由我领队
Understood.
我明白了
Then let's set off.
那么我们出发吧
So, let's go
那我们上吧
into the dungeon.
进入地下城